<nodes>	
	<node id = "Day1" >
		<text>The ritual will still take a while to finish. 
		Many thoughts cloud your mind.
		As the flames flicker, you reflect upon your life.</text>
		<choices>
		</choices>
		<consequence>0</consequence>
	</node>
	
	<node id = "Green1-0" >
		<text>You are greeted by Green, your best friend since childhood.
		Hi, White!
		How are you doing in the Occultism 101?</text>
		<choices>
			<choice to="Green1-1" >Well enough, I suppose. Listen, I need to be somewhere. (Ignore Green)</choice>
			<choice to="Green1-2" >Most excellent, do you want me to help you with it?</choice>
		</choices>
		<consequence>0</consequence>
	</node>
	<node id = "Green1-1" >
		<text>Oh, that's ok...</text>
		<choices></choices>
		<consequence>-1</consequence>
	</node>
	<node id = "Green1-2" >
		<text>Sweet, I will come by your house later tonight.</text>
		<choices></choices>
		<consequence>1</consequence>
	</node>	
	
	<node id = "Yellow1-0" >
		<text>Yellow, the school bully. He has been picking on you ever since you met.
		Where do you think you are going, White?
		Red won't have anything to do with the likes of you!</text>
		<choices>
			<choice to="Yellow1-1" >Punch Yellow right on the nose!</choice>
			<choice to="Yellow1-2" >Get lost, Yellow! (Ignore him completely)</choice>
		</choices>
		<consequence>0</consequence>
	</node>
	<node id = "Yellow1-1" >
		<text>Why, you little... (You have a little brawl with Yellow) </text>
		<choices></choices>
		<consequence>-2</consequence>
	</node>
	<node id = "Yellow1-2" >
		<text>Pffft, you won't make it with her in a million years...</text>
		<choices></choices>
		<consequence>1</consequence>
	</node>	
	
	<node id = "Red1-0" >
		<text>It's Red.... She has been on your mind lately. 
		Her enticing crimson skin, her majestic nose...
		She was a sight for sore eyes, for sure.</text>
		<choices>
			<choice to="Red1-1" >Ask Red on a romantic date.</choice>
			<choice to="Red1-2" >Hi Red. How are you today?</choice>
			<choice to="Red1-3" >Stay awkwardly silent.</choice>
		</choices>
		<consequence>0</consequence>
	</node>
	<node id = "Red1-1" >
		<text>Oh, I would love to!
		The two of you go on a date and grow very fond of each other.</text>
		<choices></choices>
		<consequence>2</consequence>
	</node>
	<node id = "Red1-2" >
		<text>Hi, White! I was just thinking about what Professor Pickman said.
		Do you also think that the practice of dactylomancy in recent media covering has been increasingly skewed.
		You spend some time chatting with Red and you grow closer.</text>
		<choices></choices>
		<consequence>1</consequence>
	</node>
		<node id = "Red1-3" >
		<text>What's the matter, White?
		Oh well, it's time for class anyway.
		You awkwardly stumble away, almost losing your footing.</text>
		<choices></choices>
		<consequence>0</consequence>
	</node>
	

</nodes>

