<nodes>	
	<!---DAY 1--->
	<node id = "Day1" >
		<text>The ritual will still take a while to finish. 
		Many thoughts cloud your mind.
		As the flames flicker, you reflect upon your life.</text>
		<choices></choices>
		<consequence>0</consequence>
	</node>
	
	<node id = "Green1-0" >
		<text>You are greeted by Green, your best friend since childhood.
		"Hi, White!"
		"How are you doing in the Occultism 101?"</text>
		<choices>
			<choice to="Green1-1" >Well enough, I suppose. Listen, I need to be somewhere. (Ignore Green)</choice>
			<choice to="Green1-2" >Most excellent, do you want me to help you with it?</choice>
		</choices>
		<consequence>0</consequence>
	</node>
	<node id = "Green1-1" >
		<text>"Oh, that's ok..."</text>
		<choices></choices>
		<consequence>-1</consequence>
	</node>
	<node id = "Green1-2" >
		<text>"Sweet, I will come by your house later tonight."</text>
		<choices></choices>
		<consequence>1</consequence>
	</node>	
	
	<node id = "Yellow1-0" >
		<text>Yellow, the school bully. He has been picking on you ever since you met.
		"Where do you think you are going, White?"
		"Red won't have anything to do with the likes of you!"</text>
		<choices>
			<choice to="Yellow1-1" >Punch Yellow right on the nose!</choice>
			<choice to="Yellow1-2" >Get lost, Yellow! (Ignore him completely)</choice>
		</choices>
		<consequence>0</consequence>
	</node>
	<node id = "Yellow1-1" >
		<text>"Why, you little..." (You have a little brawl with Yellow) </text>
		<choices></choices>
		<consequence>-2</consequence>
	</node>
	<node id = "Yellow1-2" >
		<text>"Pffft, you won't make it with her in a million years..."</text>
		<choices></choices>
		<consequence>1</consequence>
	</node>	
	
	<node id = "Red1-0" >
		<text>It's Red.... She has been on your mind lately. 
		Her enticing crimson skin, her majestic nose...
		She was a sight for sore eyes, for sure.
		"Hi, White!"</text>
		<choices>
			<choice to="Red1-1" >Ask Red on a romantic date.</choice>
			<choice to="Red1-2" >Hi, Red. How are you today?</choice>
			<choice to="Red1-3" >Stay awkwardly silent.</choice>
		</choices>
		<consequence>0</consequence>
	</node>
	<node id = "Red1-1" >
		<text>"Oh, I would love to!"
		The two of you go on a date and grow very fond of each other.</text>
		<choices></choices>
		<consequence>2</consequence>
	</node>
	<node id = "Red1-2" >
		<text>"Hi, White! I was just thinking about what Professor Pickman said."
		"Do you also think that the practice of dactylomancy in recent media covering has been increasingly skewed?"
		You spend some time chatting with Red and you grow closer.</text>
		<choices></choices>
		<consequence>1</consequence>
	</node>
		<node id = "Red1-3" >
		<text>"What's the matter, White?"
		"Oh well, it's time for class anyway."
		You awkwardly stumble away, almost losing your footing.</text>
		<choices></choices>
		<consequence>0</consequence>
	</node>
	<!---END OF DAY 1--->
	
	
	<!---DAY 2--->
	<node id = "Day2">
		<text>That's right. Green was your best friend.
		You could have taken better care of him.
		Yellow gave you quite some trouble but you never really saw or even thought about him after graduation.
		And Red. That is where it all began for you two...</text>
		<choices></choices>
		<consequence>0</consequence>
	</node>
	
	<node id = "Red2-0" >
		<text>You married Red soon after graduation.
		She started work as a news weather reporter, while you decided to focus your life on academic study of the occult.
		You are so close to a breakthrough which could change the course of the whole world.
		"White, my dear, I thought we could have a nice dinner together tonight?"</text>
		<choices>
			<choice to="Red2-1" >Sure, I will try and wrap things up earlier tonight.</choice>
			<choice to="Red2-2" >I cannot do that, the breakthrough may be revealed any day now, I have to push forward.</choice>
		</choices>
		<consequence>0</consequence>
	</node>
	<node id = "Red2-1" >
		<text>"How wonderful! I will prepare your favourite dish."</text>
		<choices></choices>
		<consequence>+2</consequence>
	</node>
	<node id = "Red2-2" >
		<text>"I see. But know that I will be waiting for you, always..."</text>
		<choices></choices>
		<consequence>-1</consequence>
	</node>	
	
	<node id = "Green2-0" >
		<text>Green has been worried about you working too hard.
		You know he means well but you still don't like being told what to do.
		"White, I never see you around anymore."
		"Aren't you pushing yourself too hard?"</text>
		<choices>
			<choice to="Green2-1" >Green, I am fine, stop worrying about me.</choice>
			<choice to="Green2-2" >You are right, I know. I will take some time off soon.</choice>
		</choices>
		<consequence>0</consequence>
	</node>
	<node id = "Green2-1" >
		<text>"Ok, White but try and keep in mind that research can wait. There is more to life."</text>
		<choices></choices>
		<consequence>-1</consequence>
	</node>
	<node id = "Green2-2" >
		<text>"I am glad to hear that. I am sure Red will appreciate it as well."</text>
		<choices></choices>
		<consequence>1</consequence>
	</node>	
	
	<!---END OF DAY 2--->
	
	
	<!---DAY 3--->
	<node id = "Day3">
		<text>Your early years were full of work.
		Had you known what was to come next, would you have acted any different?
		Maybe this is how it was supposed to be.
		This is, after all, what your research was for.
		To save lives...</text>
		<choices></choices>
		<consequence>0</consequence>
	</node>
	
	<node id = "Green3-0" >
		<text>Green has been the only person you still talk to after Red died of cancer.
		It came so unexpectedly and modern occultist medicine just wasn't up to the task.
		"White, it has been almost a year now. I know it is harsh but you have to let go of her. She isn't coming back."</text>
		<choices>
			<choice to="Green3-1" >Yeah... I am not so sure about that. How about you just leave me alone for once.</choice>
			<choice to="Green3-2" >Thank you for your support, Green. I really appreciate your friendship over all these years.</choice>
		</choices>
		<consequence>0</consequence>
	</node>
	<node id = "Green3-1" >
		<text>"Have it your way..."</text>
		<choices></choices>
		<consequence>-1</consequence>
	</node>
	<node id = "Green3-2" >
		<text>"I hope you get better soon. In fact, you are welcome to dinner at our house tonight!"
		You feel slightly better.</text>
		<choices></choices>
		<consequence>1</consequence>
	</node>	
	
	<node id = "Blue3-0" >
		<text>Blue, the Occult Detective.
		You can figure why he is here.
		You only wonder how he found out...
		"Mr. White? You have fallen under the inspection the Occultist Intelligence Bureau under the charge of illegal occultistic experiments upon humans."
		"We are hereby announcing that you currently stand under investigation; any attempt to hinder us will bring upon you a criminal charge."</text>
		<choices>
			<choice to="Blue3-1" >Kick Blue with your fist</choice>
			<choice to="Blue3-2" >I guess there is nothing I can do anymore...</choice>
		</choices>
		<consequence>0</consequence>
	</node>
	<node id = "Blue3-1" >
		<text>"Yeeaaaow... What's the big idea!? Boys, we have a scoundrel on our hands!" (You are arrested)</text>
		<choices></choices>
		<consequence>-2</consequence>
	</node>
	<node id = "Blue3-2" >
		<text>"Alright, feel free to go about your business as usual but stay out of our way."</text>
		<choices></choices>
		<consequence>1</consequence>
	</node>	
	
	<!---END OF DAY 3--->
	
	<!---DAY 4--->
	<node id = "Day4">
		<text>Blue found nothing, of course.
		It's not as if you didn't know it was illegal.
		You took every measure to cover your tracks and it paid off.
		</text>
		<choices></choices>
		<consequence>0</consequence>
	</node>
	
	<node id = "Green4-0" >
		<text>Green found out all about it though.
		He found Red, frozen, waiting.
		"What are you doing, White?"
		"This is utter madness! You cannot resurrect her! It is simply not possible!"
		"Even if it was possible, you would be found out and executed for treason."
		</text>
		<choices>
			<choice to="Green4-1" >You are wrong, Green. It is possible. I just need a few more tries. I am doing this for the good of mankind.</choice>
			<choice to="Green4-2" >Out of my way, Green! (Sock one right on his kisser)</choice>
		</choices>
		<consequence>0</consequence>
	</node>
	<node id = "Green4-1" >
		<text>"You are out of your mind, White. I are playing with fire."</text>
		<choices></choices>
		<consequence>1</consequence>
	</node>
	<node id = "Green4-2" >
		<text>"Why, White? Why?"</text>
		<choices></choices>
		<consequence>-2</consequence>
	</node>	
	<!---END OF DAY 4--->	
	
	<!---DAY 5--->
	<node id = "Day5">
		<text>Everybody has left you.
		You are finally free to complete your research.
		You will soon be reunited with Red. The ritual must work...
		</text>
		<choices></choices>
		<consequence>0</consequence>
	</node>

</nodes>

